Robert Rauschenberg papers RRFA.01 RRFA.01.TEST
RRF Test Repository
Robert Rauschenberg papers 2019TEST
1925-2008
RRF Test Repository
Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925-2008
RRFA.01.TEST
465 cubic ft.
Robert Rauschenberg, an American artist, worked in a wide range of subjects, styles, materials, and techniques and has been called a forerunner of essentially every postwar movement sinceAbstract Expressionism. He remained, however, independent of any particular affiliation. Active from the late-1940s to 2008, his practice embodied lifelong commitment to collaboration and he worked performers, printmakers, engineers, writers, artists, and artisans from around the world.
This draft ONLY includes information on the included series. Once the Robert Rauschenberg papers are completely processed, series drafts will be combined into a single "Guide to the Robert Rauschenberg papers" (finding aid), which will supersede all drafts.
Arrangement:
Organized into series: 1. Correspondence; 2. Performance; and 3. Writings and Notes
Restrictions:
The collection is unrestricted.
- Interviews
  - Parinaud, Andre / Personal Interview (includes 2004 translation), 1962, 2004 (Box INT1)
  - Klüver, Billy / Record Interviews with Artists Participating in the Popular Image Exhibition, Washington Gallery of Modern Art, 1963 (Box INT1)
  - Seckler, Dorothy / Oral History / Archives of American Art, 1965 (Box INT1)
  - Seckler, Dorothy / The Artist Speaks: Robert Rauschenberg / Art in America, 1966 (Box INT1)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard / A Conversation with Robert Rauschenberg, Paris Review, 1968 (Box INT1)
  - O.B. [?] / Personal Interview, 1971 (Box INT1)
  - Unidentified / Interview with Robert Rauschenberg / Robert Rauschenberg in Israel Exhibition, 1975 (Box INT1)
  - Smith, Philip / Personal Interview, 1976 (Box INT1)
  - Diamonstein, Barbaralee / Personal Interviews (Excerpts Only), 1977-1978 (Box INT1)
  - Unidentified / Interview with Rachel Rosenthal / Personal Interview (restricted), 1978 (Box R1)
    Restrictions
    1 folder restricted
  - Diamonstein, Barbaralee / Robert Rauschenberg and Leo Castelli / Inside New York's Art World, 1977, 1979 (Box INT1)
  - Harmel, Mark / Robert Rauschenberg / Sanibel, Captiva Islander, 1980 (Box INT1)
  - Sayag, Alain / Interview with Robert Rauschenberg, 1981 (Box INT1)
  - Rogan, Dora / Robert Rauschenberg: The Artist with Infinite Possibilities / Kathimerini, 1981 (Box INT1)
  - Garrels, Gary / "Interview with Robert Rauschenberg" / Art New England, 1981 (Box INT1)
  - Weiss, Marjorie / Lowcountry Through the Eyes of an Artist / News + Courier, 1981 (Box INT1)
  - de Smecchia, Muni / Interview with Robert Rauschenberg (Italian Transcript) / Italian Vogue, 1982 (Box INT1)
  - Unidentified / Interview with Robert Rauschenberg / Van Gogh Television, 1983 (Box INT1)
  - Rowes, Barbara / Interview with Robert Rauschenberg / People Magazine, 1983 (Box INT1)
  - Shistrote, Barbara / Interview with Robert Rauschenberg / Public Radio, 1983 (Box INT1)
  - Adler, Ed / Personal Interview, 1983 (Box INT1)
  - Higashino (Tono), Yoshiaki / Tying Work to Elephants. About the ROCI Project / Time with Creators, 1983 (Box INT1)
  - Raedeke, Paul / Interview with Rauschenberg / Photo Metro, 1983 (Box INT1)
  - Black, L. D. / Robert Rauschenberg / Splash, 1985 (Box INT1)
  - Hardy, Thomas W. / Questions on Dante Drawings, 1985 (Box INT1)
  - Sparks, Esther / Personal Interview, 1985 (Box INT1)
  - Various / Robert Rauschenberg Interviews / Bound Compilation, 1985-1987 (Box INT2)
  - Koppel, Ted / "Disintegrating Works of Art" (with Robert Rauschenberg, Larry Rivers, Bruce Guenther) / ABC News, 1986 (Box INT2)
  - Rose, Barbara / Personal Interview, 1987 (Box INT2)
  - Rosenquist, James / Personal Interview, 1987 (Box INT2)
  - Gercke, Hans / Questions on the Color Blue / Heidelberger Kunstverein, 1988 (Box INT2)
  - Kotz, Mary Lynn / "Interview with Walter Hopps", 1987 (Box INT2)
  - Simmons, Todd / Questions on Graphicstudio / Tampa Tribune, 1989? (Box INT2)
  - Maxwell, Douglas / Extra Questions for Robert Rauschenberg, 1989 (Box INT2)
  - Saff, Don and unidentified T [Thomas Buehler?] / Personal Interview, 1989 (Box INT2)
  - Unidentified / Robert Rauschenberg / Art Meets Science and Spirituality in a Changing Economy, 1990 (Box INT2)
  - Hopps, Walter / Personal Interview, 1991 (Box INT2)
  - Peterson, William / Questions on Rachel Rosenthal, 1991 (Box INT2)
  - McClintic, Miranda / Questions on Duchamp and the Found Object / Recycling Reality, 1991 (Box INT2)
  - Tracy, Robert / Questions on Designing for Dance / French Vogue, 1992 (Box INT2)
  - Yusuf, Nilgin / Questions on Issey Miyake / Marie Claire, 1992 (Box INT2)
  - Rosenthal, Mark / Robert Rauschenberg / Artists at Gemini G.E.L., 1992 (Box INT2)
  - Gauger, Budd / Questions on "Ozone" and "Earth Summit" Posters, 1992 (Box INT2)
  - Sartogo, Domitilla / Questions on Exhibit at the Guggenheim SOHO / L'Espresso, 1992 (Box INT2)
  - Graieb, Carlos / Questions Related to the Sao Paulo Biennel / Caderno 2, 1994 (Box INT2)
  - Lobacheff, Georgia / Questions / Journal de la Tarde, 1994 (Box INT2)
  - Friedman, Carol / Questions, 1995 (Box INT2)
  - Kaufman, Jason / Interview: Robert Rauschenberg / Art News Paper, 1997 (Box INT2)
  - Planca, Elisabetta / Questions for a Written Interview / Arte, 1997 (Box INT2)
  - Marlow, Tim / Robert Rauschenberg / Tate Magazine, 1998 (Box INT2)
  - Hana Dirdra / Questions / NOW Magazine, 2001 (Box INT2)
  - Voytek, Alexa / Questions for School Report, 2001 (Box INT2)
  - Perron, Wendy / Questions on Performance / Dance Magazine, 2003 (Box INT2)
  - Brooks, Rosetta / Round the Block Once or Twice / Modern Painters, 2005 (Box INT2)
  - Jager, Joachim / Questions, undated (Box INT2)
- Performance, 1961-2003 (bulk 1961-1979); 1.5 cubic feet 4 manuscript boxes
  Arrangement:
  The series is arranged alphabetically by artist, choreographer, performance group, or performance event.
  Summary:
  The Performance series contains materials related to performances in which Robert Rauschenberg created, collaborated, or participated, as well as select documentation of performances by collaborators and friends. The bulk of the series is paper documentation ranging from handwritten or typed notes, sketches, and scores by Rauschenberg and collaborators to printed materials such as flyers, posters and programs publicizing and documenting the events. Highlights of the series include Rauschenberg's costume design sketches for Merce Cunningham, Rauschenberg's notes and supply lists for his performances, and Rauschenberg's notebooks documenting his participation in multiple works by various artists.
  This series does not contain photographs or audiovisual materials. Photographs documenting performance events are located in the Photograph collection (RRFA09). Audiovisual materials documenting performance events are located in the Audiovisual collection (RRFA02). Additional materials related to Open Score can be found in the Projects and Exhibitions series under E.A.T (draft unavailable as of 1.8.2016).
  - General
    - Chronology and Descriptions, undated (Box P1)
    - Exhibition: "Rauschenberg/Performance," Cooper Union: Notes, 1983 (Box P1)
    - Press Clippings, 1962-1970, undated (Box P1, Folder (2 folders))
  - Bastard Theater
    - General: Correspondence, 1966 (Box P1)
    - 5 Choreographers in Concert, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1966 (Box P1)
  - The Bridge, 1966 (Box P1)
  - Brown, Trisha
    - General, 1976-2003; Brown, Trisha, 1936- (Box P1)
    - Carmen, Theatro di San Carlo: Signed Program and Press Clippings, 1986-1987; Brown, Trisha, 1936- (Box P1)
    - Glacial Decoy (2 folders), 1979, undated (Box P1)
    - L'Orfeo: Project Files, 1999; Brown, Trisha, 1936- (Box P1)
    - Set and Reset, Brown, Trisha, 1936-
      - General, 1983 (Box P1)
      - Financial, 1983 (Box P1, Box R1, Folder (restricted))
        1 folder restricted.
      - Photographs, 1983 (Box P1)
      - Printed Material, 1983 (Box P1)
      - Stage Set Diagrams and Notes, 1983 (Box P1)
      - Stock Film Footage Research, 1983 (Box P1)
    - Trisha Brown Dance Company, 1981-1989 (Box P1)
    - Walker Art Center Residency: Press Clippings, 1979; Brown, Trisha, 1936- (Box P1)
    - Unidentified Dance: Costume Design, undated; Brown, Trisha, 1936- (Box P1, Box R1, Folder (restricted))
  - Concert for New Paltz, January 30, 1964 (Box P2)
  - Construction of Boston (A Collaboration): Postcard, 1962 (Box P2)
  - Cunningham, Merce
    - General, 1963-2001, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - "50th Anniversary," Lincoln Center Festival, 2002; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - Aeon: Rauschenberg Notes, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - Antic Meet: Rauschenberg Notes, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - Boston Ballet: Contract, 1974; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - [Crises?]: [Cunningham?] Notes, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box OS1)
    - "Fourteenth American Dance Festival": Signed Program, 1961; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - "Merce at the Minskoff", 1977 (Box P2)
    - "Merce Cunningham and Dance Company," Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Printed Material, 1978 (Box P2)
    - Minutiae: Cunningham Statement (?), 1974 (Box P2)
    - Night Wandering: Costume Reconstruction, 1977 (Box P2)
    - Noctures: Rauschenberg Costume Designs, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box OS1)
    - Springweather and People: Rauschenberg Costume Designs, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box XOS1)
    - Summerspace: Costume Reconstruction, 1976, 1999; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - Travelogue, Cunningham, Merce
      - Finance, 1977 (Box P2)
      - Rauschenberg Notes, circa 1977 (Box P2)
      - "Tantric Geography" at Minskoff: Project Files, 1976-1977 (Box P2)
    - Tour 1961-1962: Packing List, undated; Cunningham, Merce (Box P2)
    - World Tour 1964, Cunningham, Merce
      - Itinerary, 1964 (Box P2)
      - Programs, 1964 (Box P2)
    - Unidentified Dances, Cunningham, Merce
      - Dance Scores, undated (Box P2)
      - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P2, Folder (4 folders))
    - Various Dances, Cunningham, Merce
      - Rauschenberg Lighting Notes, undated (Box OS1)
      - Rauschenberg Notebook, undated (Box P2)
  - Dunn, Judith: Speed Limit: Notes, undated; Dunn, Judith (Box P2)
  - Fahlstrom, Oyvind: Six Performances in Sweden, 1962-1964; Fahlström, Öyvind, 1928-1976 (Box P2)
  - Farber, Viola: Brazos River, Farber, Viola
    - General, 1976-1978 (Box P2)
    - Catalogue Draft, 1977 (Box P2)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box P2, Box R1, Folder (restricted))
    - David Tudor Sketch, 1976 (Box P2)
    - Notes (Including Rauschenberg Notes), 1976 (Box P2)
    - Photographs, 1976-1977 (Box P3)
    - Press Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box P3)
    - Printed Material, 1976 (Box P3)
  - "First New York Theater Rally:" Press Releases and Schedules, 1965 (Box P3)
  - "Five New York Evenings", Fahlström, Öyvind, 1928-1976; Hay, Alex; Hay, Deborah; Paxton, Steve; Tudor, David, 1926-1996; Cunningham, Merce
    - Press Clipping, 1964 (Box P3)
    - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P3)
  - Hay, Deborah
    - Serious Duet, Paxton, Steve; Hay, Deborah
      - Rauschenberg Sketches, undated (Box XOS1)
      - Score, circa 1966 (Box P3)
    - Unidentified Dance: Rauschenberg Notes, undated; Hay, Deborah (Box P3)
  - Judson Dance Theater
    - Concert for New Platz: Rauschenberg Notes, 1964 (Box P3)
    - A Concert of Dance #3 and #4, 1963 (Box P3)
    - A Concert of Dance #14, 1964 (Box P3)
    - A Concert of Dance by Trisha Brown and Deborah Hay, 1966 (Box P3)
    - A Dance Concert of Old and New Works, 1966 (Box P3)
    - Dunas, William and Harris, Gary: Wax, undated (Box P3)
  - Modern Dance Workshop, 1964 (Box P3)
  - "NOW Festival," Washington DC: Scrapbook (xerox only), 1966; Brown, Carolyn, 1927-; Hay, Alex; Paxton, Steve; Hay, Deborah; Whitman, Robert, 1935- (Box P3)
  - Paxton, Steve
    - General, undated (Box P3)
    - Deposits (performed by Deborah Hay and Steve Paxton): Score, undated; Paxton, Steve (Box P3)
    - Performance History 1962-1964 and Notes (Notebook), undated; Paxton, Steve (Box P3)
    - Unidentified Dance: [Paxton?] Notes, undated; Paxton, Steve (Box P3)
  - Rainer, Yvonne
    - "Mattress": Rauschenberg Notes, undated; Rainer, Yvonne, 1934- (Box P3)
    - "Two Evenings of Modern Dance," Wadsworth Atheneum: Poster, 1965; Rainer, Yvonne, 1934- (Box P3)
  - Rainer, Yvonne and Morris, Robert: Unidentified, 1965 (Box P3)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert
    - 3 Act Play: Rauschenberg Sketches and Notes, undated (Box P3)
    - Gold Standard, 1964 (Box P3)
    - Linoleum
      - Burt Stern's Studio Program, 1968 (Box P3)
      - Channel 13 Announcement, 1966 (Box P3)
      - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P3)
      - Score, undated (Box P3)
    - Map Room II
      - [Paxton?] Notes, undated (Box P3)
      - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P3)
    - Open Score
      - Rauschenberg Notebook, undated (Box P3)
      - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P3, Folder (2 folders))
    - Pelican: Rauschenberg Notes, circa 1963, undated (Box P3)
    - Shot Put: Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box OS1)
    - Spring Training: Supply List, undated (Box P4)
    - Untitled, International Design Conference Aspen: Project File, 1973 (Box P4)
    - Urban Round
      - School of Visual Arts Program, 1967 (Box P4)
      - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P4)
  - Stockholm Festival for Art and Technology: Visions of the Present: Planning Documents, 1966 (Box P4)
  - Surplus Dance Theater: Exchange: Paxton Notes, circa 1964 (Box P4)
  - Taylor, Paul: "Paul Taylor Dance Company"
    - General, 1978-1979, circa 1983 (Box P4, Folder (2 folders))
    - 92nd Street Y Performance: Review, 1958; Taylor, Paul, 1930- (Box P4)
    - Theatre de Arts: Program (includes 3 Epitaphs and Tracer), undated; Taylor, Paul, 1930- (Box P4)
  - "Three Events," New York University Loeb Student Center: Poster (photo reproduction only), 1967 (Box P4)
  - Whitman, Robert: The Night Time Sky: Program, 1965; Whitman, Robert, 1935- (Box P4)
  - Unidentified Choreographers
    - Unidentified [Television Score]: Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P4)
    - Unidentified [T.V. Piece]: Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P4)
    - Unidentified Performances
      - Rauschenberg Notes, undated (Box P4, Folder (2 folders))
      - Score, 1970? (Box P4)
  - Various Choreographers
    - Various Works: Rauschenberg Notebook, undated (Box P4)
- Printed Materials
  - Other People
    - General: Group Exhibitions, 1968-1992, undated (Box PM1)
    - Albers, Josef, undated (Box PM1)
    - Archer, Hazel Larsen, 2003 (Box PM1)
    - Astor, Brooke, 1983 (Box PM1)
    - Azlan Shah, Sultan of Perak, 1989 (Box PM1)
    - Bell, Larry, circa 1971 (Box PM1)
    - Beuys, Joseph, 1980 (Box PM1)
    - Bochner, Mel, 1978 (Box PM15)
    - Botkin, Henry, 1982 (Box PM1)
    - Brown, Trisha, 1977-1987 (Box PM1)
    - Cage, John, 1978-1981 (Box PM1)
    - Chamberlain, John, 1971 (Box PM1)
    - Chien, Chun-Wuei Su, 2006 (Box PM1)
    - Cunningham, Merce, 1977-1982, 2007 (Box PM1)
    - de Menil, Dominique, 1981 (Box PM1)
    - Denes, Agnes, 1978 (Box PM1)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1980 (Box PM1)
    - Fahlstrom, Oyvind (2 folders), 1973-2001, 2007, undated (Box PM15, Box PM1)
    - Felsen, Sidney B., 1999 (Box PM1)
    - Fisher, Norman, undated (Box PM1)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1977 (Box PM1)
    - Forti, Simone, undated (Box PM1)
    - Francis, Sam, undated (Box PM1)
    - Galanos, James, 1979 (Box PM1)
    - Gilbert and George, 1978, 1987 (Box PM1)
    - Girouard, Tina, 1982 (Box PM1)
    - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix, 2000 (Box PM1)
    - Gorewitz, Rubin, 1974-1988 (Box PM13)
    - Gottlieb-Roberts, Marilyn, undated (Box PM1)
    - Grosman, Tatyana, 1976-1982 (Box PM1)
    - Guston, Philip, 1981 (Box PM1)
    - Hall, Lee, 1979 (Box PM1)
    - Haring, Keith, 1989 (Box PM1)
    - Harris, Suzanne, 1980 (Box PM15)
    - Hay, Alex, 1971 (Box PM1)
    - Hay, Deborah, 1969-1980 (Box PM1)
    - Highstein, Jene, 1979 (Box PM1)
    - Hopper, Dennis, 1988 (Box PM2)
    - Howey, Nicholas, 1986 (Box PM2)
    - Huffington, Anita, 1999 (Box PM2)
    - Hulton, Pontus, 1980-1982 (Box PM15)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1986 (Box PM13)
    - Jensen, Alfred, 1991 (Box PM2)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1977-1981 (Box PM13)
    - Judd, Donald, 1977 (Box PM2)
    - Keaton, Diane, 1980 (Box PM2)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Kennedy, Ted, undated (Box PM2)
    - Kiesler, Frederick, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Kirschenbaum, Bernard, 1978 (Box PM2)
    - Krebs, Rockne, undated, 1981-1995 (Box PM2)
    - Kuhn, Christopher, 2006 (Box PM2)
    - Leonardo da Vinci, 2003 (Box PM2)
    - Lew, Jeffrey, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1975-1997 (Box PM15)
    - Lukas, Dennis, 1971 (Box PM2)
    - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1978 (Box PM2)
    - Morris, Robert, 1974 (Box PM2)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1971 (Box PM2)
    - Neuhaus, Max, 1977 (Box PM2)
    - Newman, Barnett, 1968 (Box PM2)
    - Oldenburg, Claus, 1970-1980 (Box PM2)
    - Paladino, Mimmo; Penck, A.R.; Warhol, Andy: "Terrae Motus", 1983 (Box PM2)
    - Palomero, Carmen, undated (Box PM2)
    - Paxton, Steve, 1977-1978 (Box PM2)
    - Petersen, Robert, 1975-1983 (Box PM2)
    - Picasso, Pablo: "Catch Desire by the Tail", undated (Box PM2)
    - Priede, Zig; Stockwell, Sharon, undated (Box PM2)
    - Rauschenberg, Christopher, 1976-1982 (Box PM2)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1978 (Box PM2)
    - Rockburne, Dorothea, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1974-1981 (Box PM2)
    - Ruscha, Ed (2 folders), 1971-1981 (Box PM2, Box PM15)
    - Saff, Donald, 1974-1984 (Box PM2)
    - Saint-Phalle, Niki de, 1980, undated (Box PM2)
    - Schlossberg, Edwin, circa 1988 (Box PM2)
    - Segal, George, undated (Box PM2)
    - Serra, Richard, 1978-1979 (Box PM2)
    - Simonetti, Gianni-Emilio, circa 1967 (Box PM2)
    - Marden, Brice, 1974-1980 (Box PM15)
    - Miyake, Issey, 1983 (Box PM13)
    - Gorgoni, Gianfranco, 1980 (Box PM1)
    - Sonnier, Keith, 1977 (Box PM2)
    - Stella, Frank, 1968-1980 (Box PM2)
    - Takahashi, Hisachika, 1976, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Taylor, Al, 2003 (Box PM2)
    - Taylor, Paul, 1980 (Box PM2)
    - Tevet, Nahum, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Tinguely, Jean: "Hommage to New York", 1961 (Box PM2)
    - Toovey, Andrew, 1991 (Box PM13)
    - Tudor, David, 1979 (Box PM2)
    - Twombly, Cy (2 folders), 1975-1982 (Box PM3, Box PM15)
    - Valentine, Dewain, 1979 (Box PM13)
    - Vidal, Gore, undated (Box PM3)
    - Warhol, Andy (2 folders), 1971, 1975-1982 (Box PM3)
    - Weil, Susan (3 folders), 1975-1981, 2003, undated (Box PM3, Box PM15)
    - Wesselman, Tom, 1968-1970 (Box PM3)
    - Weiss, David, 1980 (Box PM3)
    - Whitman, Robert, 1964-1979, undated (Box PM3)
    - Whitman, Simone, 1968 (Box PM3)
    - Whitman, Sylvia, 1977-1979, undated (Box PM3)
  - Other Topics
    - 112 Workshop, undated (Box PM3)
    - AIDS Project Los Angeles, 1992 (Box PM3)
    - Alyce de Roulet Williamson Gallery, 1992-1994, undated (Box PM3)
    - American Ballet Theatre, 1986-1988 (Box PM3)
    - American Federation of Arts, 1993-1994 (Box PM3)
    - André Emmerich Gallery, 1979 (Box PM4)
    - Anthology Film Archives: "Video Texts: 1983" (Box PM4)
    - Blue Sky Gallery, 1981 (Box PM4)
    - Care and Rehabilitation of Wildlife (C.R.O.W.), 1986, undated (Box PM4)
    - Centre Georges Pompidou, 1977 (Box PM4)
    - Dyslexia, Port Arthur, undated (Box PM4)
    - Groninger Museum, 1995 (Box PM4)
    - Guggenheim Museum Bilbao, 1997 (Box PM4)
    - HIV/AIDS Research Study, 1993 (Box PM4)
    - Modern Art Museum of Fort Worth, 1996 (Box PM4)
    - NY Central Art Supply Catalogs, 2000, 2004 (Box PM4)
    - Old Bahama Bay, undated (Box PM4)
    - OT Ceramics, undated (Box PM4)
    - Pace Gallery, 1979 (Box PM4)
    - P.S. 1, 1978, 1983 (Box PM4)
    - Theatre de la Claca, undated (Box PM15)
    - University Art Museum, Berkeley, CA, 1979 (Box PM4)
    - Whales, undated (Box PM4)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert
    - General
      - Barney's New York, undated (Box PM5)
      - Capital Magazine, 1977 (Box PM5)
      - Catalogue Raisonné Project, undated (Box PM5)
      - "A Chronology of Painters", 1966 (Box PM5)
      - Experiments in Art and Technology (E.A.T.): Klüver Interview, 1991 (Box PM5)
      - Hiroshima City Museum of Contemporary Art, undated (Box PM5)
      - "Inside New York's Art World", 1980 (Box PM5)
      - Museum of Modern Art: Leo Castelli's 90th, 1997 (Box PM5)
      - Museum of Modern Art, Shiga, 1988-1992 (Box PM5)
      - Oregon Art Institute, 1989 (Box PM5)
      - Postcards, undated (Box PM5)
      - Poster Originals, Limited, 1976 (Box PM5)
      - United Nations: International Conference on Population and Development, 1993 (Box PM5)
      - Universal Limited Art Editions (ULAE), 2008 (Box PM5)
      - What Creates Series, 1988-1989 (Box PM5)
    - Auctions and Art Fairs
      - Benefit Auctions, 1976 (Box PM5)
      - Novo Arts, Inc., 1983 (Box PM5)
    - Artworks
      - General: Postcards and Other Reproductions (6 folders), undated (Box PM5, Box PM6)
      - "Ace", 1965 (Box PM6)
      - "Art for 13", 1990 (Box PM6)
      - "Artist's Rights Today", 1976 (Box PM6)
      - "Bank Job", 1981 (Box PM6)
      - "Fargo Podium", 1983 (Box PM6)
      - "Last Turn—Your Turn": Democratic National Convention, 1992 (Box PM13)
      - "Noname (Elephant)" ("For Meyer Shapiro" Portfolio), 1974 (Box PM6)
      - "Pages" and "Fuses", 1975 (Box PM6)
      - "Periwinkle Shaft", 1980 (Box PM6)
      - "Pre-Morocco" ("Eight by Eight to Celebrate the Temporary Contemporary" Portfolio), circa 1983 (Box PM6)
      - "Smitty's Melon", 1981 (Box PM6)
      - "Star Quarters", 1971 (Box PM6)
      - "Statue of Liberty" ("New York, New York" Portfolio), 1983 (Box PM6)
      - "Tideline", 1987 (Box PM6)
      - "Tracks", 1976 (Box PM6)
      - "Tribute 21" (2 folders), 1998 (Box PM13, Box PM14)
    - Exhibitions
      - Group
        - Stedelijk Museum: "Dylaby", 1962 (Box PM7)
        - Yale University Art Gallery: "Contemporary Paintings Selected From 1960-1961 New York Gallery Exhibitions", 1962 (Box PM7)
        - Leo Castelli: "Ace", 1962 (Box PM7)
        - Thibaut Gallery: "According to the Letter", 1963 (Box PM7)
        - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum: "The Photographic Image", 1966 (Box PM7)
        - Expo '67, United State Pavilion: "American Painting Now", 1967 (Box PM7)
        - Dayton's Gallery 12: "Contemporary Graphics Published by Universal Limited Art Editions", 1968 (Box PM7)
        - Dwan Gallery: "Language II", 1968 (Box PM7)
        - Hayward Gallery: "Pop Art", 1969 (Box PM7)
        - National Gallery of Art: "The Artist and Space", 1969 (Box PM7)
        - General, 1970s (Box PM14)
        - Metropolitan Museum of Art: "Prints by Nine New York Painters", 1970 (Box PM7)
        - Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania: "Against Order: Chance and Art", 1970 (Box PM7)
        - Leo Castelli: "Furniture", 1972 (Box PM7)
        - Pratt Graphics Gallery: "The Language of Print", 1973 (Box PM7)
        - Margo Leavin Gallery: "Drawings", 1973 (Box PM7)
        - Musée Galliera: "Aspects de l'Art Actuel", 1973 (Box PM7)
        - Greenwich Country Day School: "ART '73", 1973 (Box PM7)
        - California State University: "The Altered Print", 1973 (Box PM7)
        - John Berggruen Gallery: "Castelli at Berggruen", 1974 (Box PM7)
        - Whitney Museum of American Art, Downtown Branch: "Clay", 1974 (Box PM7)
        - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts: "Poets of the Cities: New York and San Francisco, 1950–1965", 1974 (Box PM7)
        - Dayton's Gallery 12: "Works on Paper", 1975 (Box PM7)
        - Leo Castelli Gallery and Multiples, Inc., 1975 (Box PM7)
        - Knowlton Gallery: "Art in Boxes", 1975 (Box PM7)
        - Pace Gallery: "America: The Third Century", 1975 (Box PM7)
        - Fort Worth Art Museum: "The Great American Rodeo", 1976 (Box PM7)